<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Politics on Vivian Balakrishnan</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/Politics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Politics on Vivian Balakrishnan</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/Politics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>To care for you, protect your families, invest and build our collective destiny together</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2015/08/22/To-care-for-you-protect-your%20families-invest-and-build-our-collective-destiny-together/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2015/08/22/To-care-for-you-protect-your%20families-invest-and-build-our-collective-destiny-together/</guid>
      <description>&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/trust.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Drawing&#34; style=&#34;width: 400px;&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To care for you, protect your families, invest and build our collective destiny together - Sim Ann, Liang Eng Hwa, Christopher de Souza and I promise, as we have just announced that we will stand for election in Holland-Bukit Timah GRC. Dr Teo Ho Pin will stand again in Bukit Panjang SMC.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Dr Teo has served in Bukit Panjang for almost twenty years, most of which as Chairman of the Town Council. He is also been Mayor of North West CDC. He knows everyone, every nook and cranny of his constituency and indeed our entire GRC. Both he and I have been here since the original formation of the GRC in 2001.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating a sustainable environment, a dynamic economy and a Smart Nation is essential for us to confront some of the biggest existential challenges of our time</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2015/07/14/a-sustainable-environment-a-dynamic-economy-and-a-smart-nation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2015/07/14/a-sustainable-environment-a-dynamic-economy-and-a-smart-nation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRANSCRIPT OF SPEECH BY MINISTER FOR THE ENVIRONMENT AND WATER RESOURCES AND MINISTER-IN-CHARGE OF THE SMART NATION INITIATIVE AT THE INAUGURAL SMARTER CITIES ROUNDTABLE, 14 JUL 2015, 1015 AM&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Good morning, everyone. It is a pleasure to be here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;2&#x9;Thank you, Ms Jessica Cheam for organizing this discussion and Mr Johan de Villiers for the welcome speech.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;3&#x9;Ms Jacqueline Poh, Managing Director of Infocomm Development Authority, Singapore (IDA) and Mr Goh Chee Kiong, Director at Singapore Economic Development Board (EDB) and I are very privileged to be here.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why a Smart Nation? Because we have to ride a new wave of technology every fifty years</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2015/05/06/Why-Smart-Nation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2015/05/06/Why-Smart-Nation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SPEECH BY DR VIVIAN BALAKRISHNAN, MINISTER FOR THE ENVIRONMENT AND WATER RESOURCES, AND MINISTER-IN-CHARGE OF THE SMART NATION INITIATIVE FOR SMU’S SIM KEE BOON INSTITUTE OF FINANCIAL ECONOMICS (SKBI) ANNUAL CONFERENCE ON 6 MAY 2015, 7PM AT THE FAIRMONT HOTEL&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Mr. Lim Chee Onn, the Chairman of the Advisory Board SKBI&#xA;The family of Mr Sim Kee Boon : Ms Jeannette Sim, Mr Peter Sim&#xA;The family of Prof Winston Koh,&#xA;Prof Arnaud De Meyer, our host,&#xA;Friends, Ladies and Gentlemen&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2015/03/23/one-man&#39;s-values-and-vision/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2015/03/23/one-man&#39;s-values-and-vision/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;speech-by-dr-vivian-balakrishnan-minister-for-the-environment-and-water-resources-at-earthlink-ntus-greenfest-synergy-2015-on-23-march-2015-1140am&#34;&gt;SPEECH BY DR VIVIAN BALAKRISHNAN, MINISTER FOR THE ENVIRONMENT AND WATER RESOURCES, AT EARTHLINK NTU’s GREENFEST SYNERGY 2015, ON 23 MARCH 2015, 11.40AM&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;never-again-in-our-lifetime-will-one-mans-values-and-vision-have-such-an-impact-on-a-people-and-a-place&#34;&gt;Never again in our lifetime will one man’s values and vision have such an impact on a people and a place.&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/IMG_6062.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Drawing&#34; style=&#34;width: 400px;&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Friends, ladies and gentlemen,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We all woke up this morning to the bad news. And obviously, one of the considerations was which events do we proceed with as planned, and which do we postpone or reschedule or cancel.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A busy year for MEWR, NEA and PUB</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2014/03/11/a-busy-year-for-mewr-nea-and-pub/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2014/03/11/a-busy-year-for-mewr-nea-and-pub/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;http://vivian.balakrishnan.sg/wp-content/uploads/2014/03/BishanPark.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;BishanPark&#34; /&gt;&#xA;&lt;figcaption&gt;BishanPark&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Speech by Dr Vivian Balakrishnan, Minister for the Environment and Water Resources, Committee of Supply Debate, 11 March 2014 (Section A)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Date Published: 11 Mar 2014&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;1.      Mdm Chair, my colleagues in NEA, PUB and MEWR have had a very busy year. In the space of 12 months, we have had to confront the worst haze episode ever; the worst dengue outbreak ever; we still had a couple of localised flash floods to deal with, and now we have the most prolonged dry spell ever. February has been the driest month on record and also the windiest month on record. We seem to be bent on breaking new records all the time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lessons from campus life : Why we need to go beyond textbooks, keep an open mind and prepare for an unpredictable future</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2012/08/22/lessons_from_campus_life/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2012/08/22/lessons_from_campus_life/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;http://vivian.balakrishnan.sg/wp-content/uploads/2012/08/nussu_crest_logo_colour_-_print-300x88.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; title=&#34;NUS Students&#39; Union crest&#34; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The NUS Students&amp;#8217; Union invited me to the Union Forum on 17 August 2012 to share my reflections on life as an undergraduate.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This following is an edited transcript of an off-the-cuff speech. &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.razor.tv/site/servlet/segment/main/news/81400.html&#34;&gt;Razor TV video available&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Mr Ang Yu Qian, President of the National University of Singapore Students&amp;#8217; Union (NUSSU)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Mr Soh Yi Da, President of the National University of Singapore Students&amp;#8217; Political Association (NUSPA)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Friends, Ladies and Gentlemen,&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If we are to create a world of peace, love and harmony, we have to start by discovering ourselves
</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2012/07/22/if-we-are-to-create-a-world-of-peace-love-and-harmony-we-have-to-start-by-discovering-ourselves/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2012/07/22/if-we-are-to-create-a-world-of-peace-love-and-harmony-we-have-to-start-by-discovering-ourselves/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;http://vivian.balakrishnan.sg/wp-content/uploads/2012/07/2012-07-22-19.22.35-2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; title=&#34;2012-07-22 19.22.35-2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hindi Centres 2012 Concert&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Excerpts of a speech delivered on 22 July 2012 to commemorate the Hindi Centres Day.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Mr Vijay Kumar Rai, President of the Hindi Society Singapore; Members of the Management Committee of the Hindi Society and Hindi Centres,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are here today to celebrate 23 years of really heartfelt volunteerism. I see many of you in this room that I recognise, and was also introduced to Mrs Sharma, whom I understand has been a teacher in the Hindi Centre since it started in August 1990.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lim Hock Siew (1931-2012) &amp;#8211; a fiercely independent unbending tenacious political fighter all his life</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2012/06/05/lim-hock-siew-1931-2012-a-fiercely-independent-unbending-tenacious-political-fighter-all-his-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2012/06/05/lim-hock-siew-1931-2012-a-fiercely-independent-unbending-tenacious-political-fighter-all-his-life/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I remember meeting him 24 years ago at a party hosted by my mentor Professor. Arthur Lim. They were classmates in medical school and life long friends.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;He introduced himself as &amp;#8220;I am Lim Hock Siew, and just came out of prison a few years ago!&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We had a good chat and he freely shared his life experiences. I was struck by the absence of bitterness despite all his sacrifices. I think he knew in his heart that he was a patriot, and was proud that he never gave in.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why and how we must remain an open city</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2012/06/03/why-and-how-we-must-remain-an-open-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2012/06/03/why-and-how-we-must-remain-an-open-city/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is an excerpt of a speech I gave in Parliament in 2009. This issue remains &amp;#8216;live&amp;#8217;. We must acknowledge the valid concerns of Singaporeans about the pace of immigration and whether our infrastructure development has kept pace. We must reaffirm that Singaporean will always come first. We need an open constructive discussion about this and other sensitive issues. But we can do so in a civil and constructive tone.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
