<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Environment on Vivian Balakrishnan</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/Environment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Environment on Vivian Balakrishnan</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/Environment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2015/03/23/one-man&#39;s-values-and-vision/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2015/03/23/one-man&#39;s-values-and-vision/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;speech-by-dr-vivian-balakrishnan-minister-for-the-environment-and-water-resources-at-earthlink-ntus-greenfest-synergy-2015-on-23-march-2015-1140am&#34;&gt;SPEECH BY DR VIVIAN BALAKRISHNAN, MINISTER FOR THE ENVIRONMENT AND WATER RESOURCES, AT EARTHLINK NTU’s GREENFEST SYNERGY 2015, ON 23 MARCH 2015, 11.40AM&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;never-again-in-our-lifetime-will-one-mans-values-and-vision-have-such-an-impact-on-a-people-and-a-place&#34;&gt;Never again in our lifetime will one man’s values and vision have such an impact on a people and a place.&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/IMG_6062.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Drawing&#34; style=&#34;width: 400px;&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Friends, ladies and gentlemen,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We all woke up this morning to the bad news. And obviously, one of the considerations was which events do we proceed with as planned, and which do we postpone or reschedule or cancel.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A busy year for MEWR, NEA and PUB</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2014/03/11/a-busy-year-for-mewr-nea-and-pub/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2014/03/11/a-busy-year-for-mewr-nea-and-pub/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;http://vivian.balakrishnan.sg/wp-content/uploads/2014/03/BishanPark.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;BishanPark&#34; /&gt;&#xA;&lt;figcaption&gt;BishanPark&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Speech by Dr Vivian Balakrishnan, Minister for the Environment and Water Resources, Committee of Supply Debate, 11 March 2014 (Section A)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Date Published: 11 Mar 2014&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;1.      Mdm Chair, my colleagues in NEA, PUB and MEWR have had a very busy year. In the space of 12 months, we have had to confront the worst haze episode ever; the worst dengue outbreak ever; we still had a couple of localised flash floods to deal with, and now we have the most prolonged dry spell ever. February has been the driest month on record and also the windiest month on record. We seem to be bent on breaking new records all the time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The haze &amp;#8211; and what a difference three weeks make</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2013/07/09/the-haze-and-what-a-difference-three-weeks-make/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2013/07/09/the-haze-and-what-a-difference-three-weeks-make/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;http://vivian.balakrishnan.sg/wp-content/uploads/2013/07/Slide04.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Slide04&#34; /&gt;&#xA;&lt;figcaption&gt;Slide04&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our skies were blue and the air crystal clear today.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Had a long discussion in Parliament on the cause of the haze and our plans for the future. I thanked Singaporeans for your calmness, patience, and the fact that you refused to get rattled by the situation. It is that ability to respond sensibly, rationally, cohesively and collectively as a people that makes the difference and makes me confident that we will get through this together, whatever happens.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sustainable development makes good business sense, especially in Singapore</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2013/03/14/sustainable-development-makes-good-business-sense-especially-in-singapore/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2013/03/14/sustainable-development-makes-good-business-sense-especially-in-singapore/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;http://vivian.balakrishnan.sg/wp-content/uploads/2013/03/IMG_3077.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_3077&#34; /&gt;&#xA;&lt;figcaption&gt;IMG_3077&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The world is currently at several inflexion points. There are now more than seven billion human beings on the planet, and more than half of us live in cities. Indeed, the most essential elements of life – food, water – are now interlinked with energy, and with fossil fuels. And this portends therefore, either a potential crisis or enormous opportunities for businesses in the years ahead.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the past, great fortunes were made by simply extracting resources, mining materials – iron ore and energy – from the ground. And manufacturing grew enormously, on the back of the availability of cheap resources and cheap energy. But this era of cheap natural resources is coming to a close.  And we can now no longer afford to ignore the externalities of industrialisation and of human activities.  Pollution and global warming are real phenomena,  which affect not just the quality of the environment, but also involves huge economic costs for all of us. In other words, the old ways of getting rich are not going to be viable in the future.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Political suicide vs Demographic extinction</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2013/02/01/political-suicide-vs-demographic-extinction/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2013/02/01/political-suicide-vs-demographic-extinction/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;http://vivian.balakrishnan.sg/wp-content/uploads/2013/02/bnr_a_high_quality_living_environment.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bnr_a_high_quality_living_environment&#34; /&gt;&#xA;&lt;figcaption&gt;bnr_a_high_quality_living_environment&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Like many Singaporeans, I would also prefer to have a smaller population of foreigners in our Singapore but ……&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are facing the crisis of our lifetime. Our citizen population will halve every two generations. This is a serious &amp;#8216;long&amp;#8217; term problem and the only cure is more babies. But the real emergency is not babies, but ageing. That is why the population will increase in the short term before the inevitable decrease in the long term.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the actions of an anti-social minority damage our neighbourhood</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2012/11/21/how-the-actions-of-an-anti-social-minority-damage-our-neighbourhood/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2012/11/21/how-the-actions-of-an-anti-social-minority-damage-our-neighbourhood/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;http://vivian.balakrishnan.sg/wp-content/uploads/2012/11/litter.jpeg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; title=&#34;litter&#34; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Many of our void decks have facilities for the convenience of residents. These serve as open communal spaces for fellowship and bonding activities. Unfortunately, this scene is all too common.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A local resident emailed me – and the issues he brought up are pertinent. It illustrates the real problems we have on the ground – and the difficult choices we have to make. I have extracted our anonymised email exchange below and would be grateful for your suggestions:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Increasing peer pressure for a clean and green Singapore</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2012/11/17/increasing-peer-pressure-for-a-clean-and-green-singapore/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2012/11/17/increasing-peer-pressure-for-a-clean-and-green-singapore/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://vivian.balakrishnan.sg/wp-content/uploads/2012/09/A-clean-city.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; title=&#34;A clean city&#34; /&gt;Public reaction and support for Singapore to reclaim our status as one of the cleanest cities in the world has been very encouraging. I am grateful for all the many ideas and suggestions over the past few weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One key element has been the need for increased and coordinated peer pressure, including empowering volunteers. NEA will conduct a special training course for senior members of environmental NGOs that will commence in January 2013. These volunteers will then be issued with authority cards which will enable them to identify and take enforcement action against recalcitrant persons who insist on littering. This will give them both moral and legal authority to set standards for our society.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our world is changing profoundly at an unprecedented rate. We need a coalition of the government, private companies and NGOs to protect human welfare, the fragile ecosystem and biodiversity. We have to get the economics right too.
</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2012/11/09/economics-of-ecosystems-and-biodiversity-for-business-coalition/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2012/11/09/economics-of-ecosystems-and-biodiversity-for-business-coalition/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://vivian.balakrishnan.sg/wp-content/uploads/2012/11/TEEBLaunch.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; title=&#34;TEEBLaunch&#34; /&gt;Transcript of my speech at the launch of the &amp;#8220;The Economics of Ecosystems and Biodiversity for Business Coalition&amp;#8221; at the Singapore Botanic Gardens on 6 November 2012&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We live in a world, which perhaps unwittingly, has gone through a series of inflexion points at a rate which is unprecedented. Let me cite a few of these.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First, our world population has now exceeded seven billion. Clearly, that is unprecedented. Not only that, but for the first time ever in human history, more than half of all human beings live in a city, and not in the rural countryside. This is another world first.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why governments, private sector and citizens all over the world need to collectively confront the looming crises of demographics, urbanisation, food-water-energy shortages, biodiversity, environmental integrity and human welfare
</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2012/11/06/sustainable-development-governments-private-sector-and-citizens-need-to-collectively-solve-the-looming-challenges-of/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2012/11/06/sustainable-development-governments-private-sector-and-citizens-need-to-collectively-solve-the-looming-challenges-of/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I attended the launch of the Economics of Ecosystems and Biodiversity for Business Coalition on 6 November 2012.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Our world has rapidly passed through a series of inflexion points.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;First, our world population has exceeded 7 billion.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Second, more than half of all human beings live in cities.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Third, the age of cheap and plentiful natural resources – when we could literally scrape coal, iron ore, oil, gas easily from the surface of the planet – is ending.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fourth, we are running out of fresh water on a global scale.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fifth, the nexus between energy, water and food means we desperately need another agricultural revolution in the next decade or so.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Sixth, we cannot afford to continue to simply dump pollutants, waste, toxins and carbon dioxide into the atmosphere and seas regardless of their impact on human health and safety and planetary ecology.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Seventh, globalisation and information revolution has created enormous opportunities for billions of people from developing countries, but it has also created enormous competitive pressure on everyone. It has completely transformed the nature and value of employment and enterprise in half a century – probably a rate of change that is unparalleled in human history. It has also increased disparities between those able to exploit opportunities and those left behind.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sustainable development&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winning design of new Bukit Panjang Hawker Centre unveiled</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2012/10/20/winning-design-of-new-bukit-panjang-hawker-centre-unveiled/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2012/10/20/winning-design-of-new-bukit-panjang-hawker-centre-unveiled/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;http://vivian.balakrishnan.sg/wp-content/uploads/2012/10/BPHawkerCentre.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; title=&#34;BPHawkerCentre&#34; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The BPHC design competition was launched on 11 June 2012 to commemorate the construction of the first hawker centre after 27 years. The NEA and the SIA co-organised the design competition for Bukit Panjang Hawker Centre and invited local architects to submit fresh ideas that could serve both the social and functional needs of the community. Special considerations were to be given to designs which proved attractive, practical and environmentally sustainable.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singapore: A Clean or Cleaned City? &amp;#8211; &amp;#8220;A clean city is a strong reflection of our moral and civic values&amp;#8221;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2012/09/15/singapore-a-clean-or-cleaned-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2012/09/15/singapore-a-clean-or-cleaned-city/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;http://vivian.balakrishnan.sg/wp-content/uploads/2012/09/A-clean-city.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; title=&#34;A clean city&#34; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Speech delivered at the 10th anniversary of the National Environment Agency on 15 September 2012.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We celebrate 10 years of NEA&amp;#8217;s partnership with all the stakeholders in our community to safeguard, nurture and cherish Singapore&amp;#8217;s environment. In fact, this common cause dates back much longer – and we also remember the pioneers who formed the Ministry of the Environment almost 40 years ago on 16 Sep 1972.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;During a recent trip to Tokyo, I asked to meet street cleaners. The diplomat who accompanied me told me this was not possible. She said there were no street cleaners. But when I looked out of the car, the street was spotless. She then recounted how she was scolded when she first arrived in Tokyo and tried to eat a sandwich as she strolled along the street. People stared at her, and told her pointedly not to mess up the street.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;This episode made me pause to think about our own city. We are a very densely populated city. We have made tremendous efforts over the past decades to make Singapore Clean and Green. We have had many campaigns, instituted heavy fines, stepped up enforcement and employed an army of cleaners.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We have done reasonably well so far, but I want to offer one question for public discussion:&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Singapore – A Clean or Cleaned city?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congratulations to Carrie-Anne Ng Tian Ling, Nicholas Lim Jun Yong and Luigi Marshall Cham from Anderson JC for winning Stockholm Junior Water Prize
</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2012/08/31/congratulations-to-carrie-anne-ng-tian-ling-nicholas-lim-jun-yong-and-luigi-marshall-cham-from-anderson-jc-for-winning-stockholm-junior-water-prize/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2012/08/31/congratulations-to-carrie-anne-ng-tian-ling-nicholas-lim-jun-yong-and-luigi-marshall-cham-from-anderson-jc-for-winning-stockholm-junior-water-prize/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;http://vivian.balakrishnan.sg/wp-content/uploads/2012/08/7889278536_f7416ed70f_o-300x199.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; title=&#34;7889278536_f7416ed70f_o&#34; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Carrie-Anne Ng Tian Ling, Nicholas Lim Jun Yong and Luigi Marshall Cham of Anderson Junior College made Singapoer proud by winning the Stockholm Junior Water Prize with their research project on using clay to remove pollutants from wastewater. They received their prize from Crown Princess Victoria of Sweden at the World Water Week in Stockholm on the 29th August 2012.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are all very proud of you !&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving the quality of air in Singapore</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2012/08/23/improving-quality-of-air-in-singapore/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2012/08/23/improving-quality-of-air-in-singapore/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;MultiMarkdown was unable to parse this file.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It is not possible to predict the future. But we must evolve, and cope with the consequences of future megatrends, e.g. climate change, extreme storms, extended droughts, water scarcity, land scarcity, energy costs, resource scarcity and food production
</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2012/07/30/it-is-not-possible-to-predict-the-future-but-we-must-evolve-and-cope-with-the-consequences-of-future-megatrends-e-g-climate-change-extreme-storms-extended-droughts-water-scarcity-land-scarcity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2012/07/30/it-is-not-possible-to-predict-the-future-but-we-must-evolve-and-cope-with-the-consequences-of-future-megatrends-e-g-climate-change-extreme-storms-extended-droughts-water-scarcity-land-scarcity/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;PUB recently announced &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.pub.gov.sg/mpublications/Pages/PressReleases.aspx#&#34; title=&#34;PUB press release - 19 July 2012&#34;&gt;new measures to increase flood protection&lt;/a&gt; at upstream areas of the Stamford Canal catchment area, including Orchard Road.The new measures include the construction of a new diversion canal to divert stormwater from about 240 hectares, or 38%, of the Stamford Canal catchment to Singapore River. Complementing the diversion canal is a &lt;a href=&#34;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Detention_basin&#34;&gt;detention tank&lt;/a&gt; which will be built to capture excess stormwater from the existing drains along Holland Road. These measures will enhance drainage capacity for this upstream area and protect it against potentially more intense storms in the future.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build the most beautiful city you can; plant as many trees as you can; invest in the latest technology; conserve water, energy and resources; and find honest, competent and visionary leadership
</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2012/07/02/build-the-most-beautiful-city-you-can-plant-as-many-trees-as-you-can-invest-in-the-latest-technology-conserve-water-energy-and-resources-and-find-honest-competent-and-visionary-leadership/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2012/07/02/build-the-most-beautiful-city-you-can-plant-as-many-trees-as-you-can-invest-in-the-latest-technology-conserve-water-energy-and-resources-and-find-honest-competent-and-visionary-leadership/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://vivian.balakrishnan.sg/wp-content/uploads/2012/07/20120704-213933.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; title=&#34;20120704-213933.jpg&#34; /&gt;I spoke at the Opening Plenary of the Singapore International Water Week 2012, World Cities Summit and CleanEnviro Summit. Professor Tommy Koh, who was the moderator, asked:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8220;Minister, my question to you is two-fold. First, this plenary brings together our colleagues from water, city and the environment. What is the common thread that ties the three together, and what are some lessons learned that you would like to share with us?&amp;#8221; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Design competition for new Bukit Panjang Hawker Centre</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2012/06/08/design-competition-for-new-bukit-panjang-hawker-centre/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2012/06/08/design-competition-for-new-bukit-panjang-hawker-centre/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;NTUC Foodfare to be appointed manager of the new Bukit Panjang Hawker Centre.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;NEA-SIA Design Competition For BPHC&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A design competition co-organised by NEA and the Singapore Institute of Architects (SIA) will be launched on 11 June for the design of the upcoming BPHC. NEA is seeking innovative new ideas from architects that address the local identity and context. In particular, special consideration will be placed on designs that are attractive, practical, cost effective, environmentally sustainable and promote social bonding.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A sustainable future for Singapore</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2012/03/06/a-sustainable-future-for-singapore/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2012/03/06/a-sustainable-future-for-singapore/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Speech delivered in Parliament on 6 March 2012 during Committee of Supply&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A SUSTAINABLE FUTURE&#xA;I thank members of the House for their questions and their suggestions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;2       There are three broad themes behind all of MEWR&amp;#8217;s programmes. First, to ensure that we continue to have a very high quality of life in Singapore;  second, to do our part in an inclusive society, in particular, to always leave a low cost option on the table and also provide opportunities for fair wages and good jobs; and third, to make sure that we have a sustainable future.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
