<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cleaners on Vivian Balakrishnan</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/Cleaners/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cleaners on Vivian Balakrishnan</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/Cleaners/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A busy year for MEWR, NEA and PUB</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2014/03/11/a-busy-year-for-mewr-nea-and-pub/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2014/03/11/a-busy-year-for-mewr-nea-and-pub/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;http://vivian.balakrishnan.sg/wp-content/uploads/2014/03/BishanPark.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;BishanPark&#34; /&gt;&#xA;&lt;figcaption&gt;BishanPark&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Speech by Dr Vivian Balakrishnan, Minister for the Environment and Water Resources, Committee of Supply Debate, 11 March 2014 (Section A)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Date Published: 11 Mar 2014&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;1.      Mdm Chair, my colleagues in NEA, PUB and MEWR have had a very busy year. In the space of 12 months, we have had to confront the worst haze episode ever; the worst dengue outbreak ever; we still had a couple of localised flash floods to deal with, and now we have the most prolonged dry spell ever. February has been the driest month on record and also the windiest month on record. We seem to be bent on breaking new records all the time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singapore: A Clean or Cleaned City? &amp;#8211; &amp;#8220;A clean city is a strong reflection of our moral and civic values&amp;#8221;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2012/09/15/singapore-a-clean-or-cleaned-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2012/09/15/singapore-a-clean-or-cleaned-city/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;http://vivian.balakrishnan.sg/wp-content/uploads/2012/09/A-clean-city.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; title=&#34;A clean city&#34; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Speech delivered at the 10th anniversary of the National Environment Agency on 15 September 2012.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We celebrate 10 years of NEA&amp;#8217;s partnership with all the stakeholders in our community to safeguard, nurture and cherish Singapore&amp;#8217;s environment. In fact, this common cause dates back much longer – and we also remember the pioneers who formed the Ministry of the Environment almost 40 years ago on 16 Sep 1972.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;During a recent trip to Tokyo, I asked to meet street cleaners. The diplomat who accompanied me told me this was not possible. She said there were no street cleaners. But when I looked out of the car, the street was spotless. She then recounted how she was scolded when she first arrived in Tokyo and tried to eat a sandwich as she strolled along the street. People stared at her, and told her pointedly not to mess up the street.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;This episode made me pause to think about our own city. We are a very densely populated city. We have made tremendous efforts over the past decades to make Singapore Clean and Green. We have had many campaigns, instituted heavy fines, stepped up enforcement and employed an army of cleaners.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We have done reasonably well so far, but I want to offer one question for public discussion:&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Singapore – A Clean or Cleaned city?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
