<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Air Quality on Vivian Balakrishnan</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/Air-quality/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Air Quality on Vivian Balakrishnan</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/Air-quality/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A busy year for MEWR, NEA and PUB</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2014/03/11/a-busy-year-for-mewr-nea-and-pub/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2014/03/11/a-busy-year-for-mewr-nea-and-pub/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;http://vivian.balakrishnan.sg/wp-content/uploads/2014/03/BishanPark.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;BishanPark&#34; /&gt;&#xA;&lt;figcaption&gt;BishanPark&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Speech by Dr Vivian Balakrishnan, Minister for the Environment and Water Resources, Committee of Supply Debate, 11 March 2014 (Section A)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Date Published: 11 Mar 2014&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;1.      Mdm Chair, my colleagues in NEA, PUB and MEWR have had a very busy year. In the space of 12 months, we have had to confront the worst haze episode ever; the worst dengue outbreak ever; we still had a couple of localised flash floods to deal with, and now we have the most prolonged dry spell ever. February has been the driest month on record and also the windiest month on record. We seem to be bent on breaking new records all the time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our world is changing profoundly at an unprecedented rate. We need a coalition of the government, private companies and NGOs to protect human welfare, the fragile ecosystem and biodiversity. We have to get the economics right too.
</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2012/11/09/economics-of-ecosystems-and-biodiversity-for-business-coalition/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2012/11/09/economics-of-ecosystems-and-biodiversity-for-business-coalition/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://vivian.balakrishnan.sg/wp-content/uploads/2012/11/TEEBLaunch.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; title=&#34;TEEBLaunch&#34; /&gt;Transcript of my speech at the launch of the &amp;#8220;The Economics of Ecosystems and Biodiversity for Business Coalition&amp;#8221; at the Singapore Botanic Gardens on 6 November 2012&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We live in a world, which perhaps unwittingly, has gone through a series of inflexion points at a rate which is unprecedented. Let me cite a few of these.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First, our world population has now exceeded seven billion. Clearly, that is unprecedented. Not only that, but for the first time ever in human history, more than half of all human beings live in a city, and not in the rural countryside. This is another world first.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving the quality of air in Singapore</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2012/08/23/improving-quality-of-air-in-singapore/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2012/08/23/improving-quality-of-air-in-singapore/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;MultiMarkdown was unable to parse this file.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
