<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Computers on Vivian Balakrishnan</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/Computers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Computers on Vivian Balakrishnan</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/Computers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Creating a sustainable environment, a dynamic economy and a Smart Nation is essential for us to confront some of the biggest existential challenges of our time</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2015/07/14/a-sustainable-environment-a-dynamic-economy-and-a-smart-nation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2015/07/14/a-sustainable-environment-a-dynamic-economy-and-a-smart-nation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRANSCRIPT OF SPEECH BY MINISTER FOR THE ENVIRONMENT AND WATER RESOURCES AND MINISTER-IN-CHARGE OF THE SMART NATION INITIATIVE AT THE INAUGURAL SMARTER CITIES ROUNDTABLE, 14 JUL 2015, 1015 AM&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Good morning, everyone. It is a pleasure to be here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;2&#x9;Thank you, Ms Jessica Cheam for organizing this discussion and Mr Johan de Villiers for the welcome speech.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;3&#x9;Ms Jacqueline Poh, Managing Director of Infocomm Development Authority, Singapore (IDA) and Mr Goh Chee Kiong, Director at Singapore Economic Development Board (EDB) and I are very privileged to be here.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why a Smart Nation? Because we have to ride a new wave of technology every fifty years</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2015/05/06/Why-Smart-Nation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2015/05/06/Why-Smart-Nation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SPEECH BY DR VIVIAN BALAKRISHNAN, MINISTER FOR THE ENVIRONMENT AND WATER RESOURCES, AND MINISTER-IN-CHARGE OF THE SMART NATION INITIATIVE FOR SMU’S SIM KEE BOON INSTITUTE OF FINANCIAL ECONOMICS (SKBI) ANNUAL CONFERENCE ON 6 MAY 2015, 7PM AT THE FAIRMONT HOTEL&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Mr. Lim Chee Onn, the Chairman of the Advisory Board SKBI&#xA;The family of Mr Sim Kee Boon : Ms Jeannette Sim, Mr Peter Sim&#xA;The family of Prof Winston Koh,&#xA;Prof Arnaud De Meyer, our host,&#xA;Friends, Ladies and Gentlemen&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I believe in Open Source</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2015/03/13/Open-Source/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2015/03/13/Open-Source/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I enjoyed the ‪#‎FOSSASIA‬ conference today with fellow geeks, developers and advocates of the ‪#‎OpenSource‬ community. Had some fun showing how NEA’s latest APIs on air quality could be accessed using simple self-taught Javascript in the Node Red system.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I believe in ‪#‎OpenData‬ and #OpenSource tools. They help build credibility and trust in government data and systems, especially when provided in real time. Even more crucial, they allow us to take collective ownership of the challenges confronting our society, and co-create solutions together. This is how we build a more innovative ecosystem, with fertile ground for entrepreneurs and enterprises. Ideas can flourish, compete and combine in novel ways. We can build a more open, transparent society with a right balance between cooperation and competition.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart Nation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2014/11/24/Smart-Nation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2014/11/24/Smart-Nation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SmartNation - Empowering Everyone Everything Everywhere&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are living through a once-in-a-lifetime revolution.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cloud computing, mobile devices, ubiquitous communications and sensors, robotics, 3D manufacturing, big data analytics and social media are causing a revolution in the way we live, learn, work, play, interact and organise our society.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These developments present enormous opportunities if we systematically empower ourselves with the new tools, new skills, new institutions and new infrastructure needed for the digital age.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s in Dr Vivian Balakrishnan&#39;s gadget boxes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2014/04/23/whats-in-dr-vivian-balakrishnans-gadget-boxes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2014/04/23/whats-in-dr-vivian-balakrishnans-gadget-boxes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;By day, he has to deal with the haze, floods and other acts of God, but by night, Environment and Water Resources Minister Vivian Balakrishnan is a self-confessed techie who fixes his own gadgets.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As a boy, he began by hacking computer games.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8220;As far as games were concerned, I wasn&amp;#8217;t very good at them,&amp;#8221; he said with a laugh.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8220;I learnt to program in order to hack the games,&amp;#8221; said Dr Balakrishnan, 53.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thrilled to meet Steve Wozniak &amp;#8211; and why Singapore needs to quickly build up critical mass of engineers, artists and angel investors</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2013/08/31/thrilled-to-meet-steve-wozniak-and-why-singapore-needs-to-quickly-build-up-critical-mass-of-engineers-artists-and-angel-investors/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2013/08/31/thrilled-to-meet-steve-wozniak-and-why-singapore-needs-to-quickly-build-up-critical-mass-of-engineers-artists-and-angel-investors/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;http://vivian.balakrishnan.sg/wp-content/uploads/2013/08/wozniak-e1377880739128-768x1024.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;wozniak&#34; /&gt;&#xA;&lt;figcaption&gt;wozniak&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thrilled to meet Steve Wozniak – and to discuss why Singapore needs to quickly build a critical mass of engineers, artists and angel investors.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We spoke at the Midas Touch Asia 2013 Enterprise Award ceremony on 26 August.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Edited excerpts of my speech – on Singapore&amp;#8217;s prospects for making an impact on the ICT revolution.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In 1982, my father bought my first computer – it was an Apple II Plus. Many of you here are too young to have used that venerable piece of technology.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
